welcome brothers and sisters to another
Wednesday question and answer will we
open up with the Ten Commandments that
God commanded the whole world to keep
brother James yes sir and God spake all
these words saying I am the Lord thy God
which have brought thee out of the land
of Egypt out of the house of bondage
Thou shalt have no other gods before me
thou shallal not make unto thee any
Graven image or any likeness of anything
that is in heaven above or that is in
the earth beneath or that is in the
water under the Earth Thou shalt not bow
down thyself to them nor serve them for
I the Lord thy God am a jealous God
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me
and showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shalt thou labor and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it Thou
shalt not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man's servant nor
thy maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for in
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in them is and
rested the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hollowed it honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee Thou shalt not kill Thou shalt not
commit adultery Thou shalt not steal
Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house Thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife nor is man
man servant nor his maid servant nor his
Ox nor his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors I read Exodus 20:
1-17 may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of his word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time time the
questions we will not answer are the
vague and the long scripture questions
as well as questions of debate we're not
here to debate we are here to spread the
true Gospel of Jesus so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible
no other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind that this is a live stream so
feel free to send in your questions at
pertain to everlasting life we just ask
that you keep your questions to a two
scripture maximum but let me introduce
to you the family that'll be taking part
on the panel this evening got brother
Dre good
evening brother Julius good evening
everybody brother Jerome Grace and
peace brother James good evening
everyone sister Deborah good evening
brother Sean
good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deb let's begin with our first
question of the evening okay there are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A Israelite by Brandon says
I keep the Commandments and try my heart
is to follow the Bible but I haven't
been baptized yet does God through Jesus
the Christ recognize me
still all right so you're trying to keep
the Commandments is good but you haven't
been baptized yet are you
recognized by God just call
him okay first let's see how you get
God's attention in the first place okay
yep so go to
Malachi thir
chapter and uh read verses 16 and
17 m okay that's Malachi the 3r chapter:
16-1 17 they say then they that feared
the Lord spake often one to another and
the Lord hearkened and heard it and a
book of remembrance was written before
him for them that feared the Lord and
thought upon his name and they shall be
mine sayeth the Lord of hosts and that
day when I make up my jewels and I will
spare them as a man spareth his own son
that serveth
him now these are people that really uh
uh fear the lord and speak off of his
name but because you say that you've
done all he said don't necessarily mean
that you belong to him let's go to
Matthew the 7th chapter read verses 21-
23 okay Matthew
7:
21-23 says not everyone that saith unto
me Lord Lord shall enter into the
kingdom of heaven but he that doeth the
will of My Father which is in heaven
many will say to me in that day Lord
Lord have we not prophesied in thy name
and that thy name have cast out devils
and in thy name done many wonderful
works and then will I profess unto them
I never knew you depart from me ye that
work iniquity
so if you speaking often of his name but
you are not doing what he said and
obeying his
Commandments then he going to tell you
at the end of the day I never knew you
and one of the things you got to do if
God is going to know you and you going
to reap the proceeds of the Covenant
that he made which is the promises to
Abraham because he's the one the only
one that ever God made promises to so
let's go look at that let's see how you
get into that let's go into Galatians
the 3r chapter read verses 26-
29 okay Galatians the 3 chapter verses
26- 29 says for ye are all the children
of God by faith in Christ Jesus for as
many of you as have been baptized into
Christ have put on Christ there is
neither Jew nor Greek there is neither
Bond nor free there is neither male nor
female for ye are all one in Christ
Jesus and if ye be Christ then ye then
are ye Abraham's seed and HS according
to the
promise so in order for you to be Christ
you got to be
baptized in order for you to reap the
promise that God made to Abraham and
that's everybody and Abraham is the only
one that made a covenant and his seed
that's physical and spiritual so now you
can keep all the Commandments and do
everything thing you want but if you
don't get baptized he don't know
you that's all they got to say all right
we hope that answers your question as we
move on to our next one next one Epatha
asked for you to explain Exodus 33 verse
23 it says his face shall not be seen
But in Exodus
24 verses 10 and 11 both verses say they
saw the god of Israel and he did not lay
his hands up on them Moses saw God so
why the
covering let's go to that Exodus the
33rd chapter and pick it up at that
verse 23 and guess caller take it from
there okay Exodus 33 and 23 says and I
will take away mine hand and thou shalt
see my back Parts but my face shall not
be seen
now go to Exodus 24 and read verses 10
and 11 okay Exodus 24: 10 and 11 say and
they saw the god of Israel and there was
under his feet as it were a paved work
of sapphire stone and as it were the
body of Heaven in its clearness and upon
the Nobles of the children of Israel he
laid not his hand also they saw God and
did eat and
drink and so did Moses see God when he
was up there but he saw the backside and
the same thing these it didn't say here
that they saw his face because he said
you can't you see my face and live and
he was very very uh careful when he was
up there with Moses that's why he put
his hand over Moses and didn't move it
until he had passed by and he saw his
backside so these guys saw the same
thing but they did not see his face it's
not written nowhere right here where it
saw his face so what Moses did and what
Moses and the other 7 73 Elders saw did
was the same thing they saw God but not
his
face that's it all right hope that
answered your question there as we move
on to our next one next one time out
Houston asked where does v baptism come
from and is is it part of the Old
Testament
law all right brother Dre where does the
baptism come from what you say brother
so ordained by the Lord let's go to uh 1
Corinthians 10 see it it
is mentioned in the New
[Music]
Testament but it is talking about what
happened in the Old Testament so 1
Corinthians 10 and pick it up at verse
one read 1 to four okay moreover
Brethren I would not that you should be
ignorant how that all our fathers were
under the cloud and all passed through
the sea and were all baptized unto Moses
in the cloud and in the sea and did eat
all the same spiritual meat and did all
drink the same spiritual drink for they
drank of that spiritual rock that
followed them and that rock was Christ
and you notice it says in verse two that
they were all baptized onto Moses in the
cloud and in the sea this is where that
happened at when they passed through the
Red Sea now let's let's go look at
something else let's go to Romans six
because baptism represents the death
burial and resurrection of Jesus Christ
so Romans 6 and pick it up at verse one
uh Romans 6 let's let's just
pick it up in two brother
okay God forbid
how verse one
okay Romans 6 and verse one says what
shall we say then shall we continue in
sin that Grace May abound God forbid how
shall we that are dead to sin live any
longer
therein know ye not that so many of us
as were baptized into Jesus Christ were
baptized into his death
therefore therefore we are buried with
him by baptism into death that like as
Christ was raised up from the dead by
the glory of the father even so we also
shall also should walk in newness of
life so when you baptize onto Christ you
baptized onto his death you go into
there and you go up under the water you
come up out of that water to walk in the
newness of
life and let's go look at one other
place Mark
16 and pick it up read verse 15 and 16
so baptism is absolutely necessary like
the guest caller pointed out in the
first question so Mark 16 15 and 16 go
ahead brother okay and he said unto them
go ye into all the world and preach the
gospel to Every Creature he that
believeth and is baptized shall be saved
but he that believeth not shall be
damned we have to not just believe but
it says he that believeth and is
baptized but this baptism represents
again the death burial and resurrection
that old man goes in that water and he
comes out to walk in the newness of of
life I hope that yeah that's right
brother because this book tell us we
have to be baptized in Jesus name
absolutely and not titles the Father the
Son and the Holy Ghost thank you for
that brother hope that answer their
question as we move on to our next next
one Malik Shakur says the people that
are ignorant of the laws do they get a
pass because some people really work
hard to study the scriptures so they can
make it into the
kingdom well the Lord said he's he's no
respect of person you know he will
punish the king as much as he will
punish the the brother that um don't
have no goals or Ambitions but let's go
into um let's go into Ecclesiastes 12
and let's see what it says
here okay because we're going to give
you some
advice on how to make your calling and
your election C sure too Ecclesiastes 12
brother when you get there read that
verse 9 and 10 for me first go and
moreover because the preacher was wise
he still taught the people knowledge yay
he gave good heed and sought out and set
in order many Proverbs the preach go
ahead brother the preacher sought to
find out acceptable words and that which
was written was upright even words of
truth so first of all you got to make
sure that you sitting before a preacher
that's teaching you the truth the true
word of God that is going to be your
great defense to make sure that you have
done all you could to stand so that's
key skip down to 13 and 14 because they
was acting about getting a pass what
does it say let us hear the conclusion
of the whole matter fear God and keep
his Commandments for this is the whole
duty of man for God shall bring every
work into judgment with every secret
thing whether it be good or whether it
be evil so that's the man at the top of
the mountain as well as the man that
might be at the bottom of the hill that
applies to them both turn over brother
to um 2 Corinthians 5 and we GNA read
one verse there and then one more after
that 2 Corinthians the 5th chapter and
read that one verse
10 because it's going to back up what we
just read in
Ecclesiastes for we must all appear
before the Judgment seat of Christ that
everyone may receive the things done in
his body according to that he hath done
whether it be good or bad and that
applies to the man at the top as well as
the man at the bottom now turn over to
Romans
10 Romans 10
and pick it up at that verse uh one for
me because like we read early about
making sure that you got a preacher
that's teaching you the truth so that
you don't fall into this trap right here
read verse one Brethren my heart's
desire and prayer to God for Israel is
that they might be
saved for I bear them record that they
have a Zeal of God but not according to
knowledge that's why you have to be
taught so you don't fall in this where
you got a great Zeal and desire to learn
God but you don't have no truth or no
knowledge on your side read that next
verse three for they being ignorant of
God's righteousness and going about to
establish their own righteousness have
not submitted themselves unto the
righteousness of God so you have to
avoid that because you don't want to be
ignorant of God's righteousness and when
you talk correct and true hey you can't
avoid that and then you have the weapons
it take to save yourself from this UNT
generation that's all I
got and keep tuning in with us because
we definitely teach the truth all right
hope that answers your question let's
move on to our next one
brother moving on just know says so is
it not a sin to own another human as a
slave forever and pass them down to your
children gu
caller go to First John 3 and 4 and read
it first John 3
and4
says 1 John 3 and4 says whoo ever
committeth sin transgresses also the law
for sin is the trans transgression of
the law that's what sin is until I can
put sin in front of the rest of it I
have to leave it alone I can't read it I
have to give you my opinion and I don't
give no opinions that's all I have to
say all right hope that shares some
light on you as we move on to our next
question yes moving on this question has
been answered before uh Zion says so the
people that are not keeping Commandments
have the same privilege of making it
into the Wilderness as someone that
keeps
them yeah yeah they both had the same
opportunity to get into the Wilderness
but um but once you get there you're
going to be obedient and keep the law or
you won't be breathing no
more so that lesson was that question
was also expounded on last week but
guess caller go ahead you gonna leave it
look it depends on when you go in the
wilderness and what you're doing let's
go into Revelation the 12th
chapter we're going to read 1 two and
Skip down and read five and six okay
Revelation 12 verse 1 2 1 and two and
then five and six it says and there
appeared a great Wonder in heaven a
woman clothed with the sun and the moon
under her feet and upon her head a crown
of 12 stars and being with child cried
travailing in birth and pain to be
delivered verse 5 and six says and she
brought forth a Manchild who was to rule
all nations with a rod of iron and her
child was caught up unto God and to his
throne and the woman fled Into the
Wilderness where she hath a place
prepared of God that they should feed
her there
1,23 score days now these are people
that's going to do this are people that
have
knowledge and have been following God
now whether somebody decide to go to a
none people that don't keep keep your
commandment decide to run with her I
doubt that they won't even know what's
going on they probably be standing on
the sideline thinking we're stupid and
foolish but as for the will is concerned
everybody goes to the Wilderness and
everybody gets the same chame let's go
in at the same chance go to Ezekiel the
20th
chapter and read from 33 to
38 Ezekiel
20:
33-38 says as I live sayeth the Lord God
surely with a mighty hand and with a
stretched out arm and with Fury poured
out will I rule over you and I will
bring you out from the people and will
gather you out of the countries wherein
ye are scattered with a Mighty hand and
with a stretched out arm with and with
Fury poured out and I will bring you
into the Wilderness of the people and
there will I plead with you face to face
like like as I pleaded with your fathers
in the wilderness of the land of Egypt
so will I plead with you sayeth the Lord
God and I will cause you to pass under
the rod and I will bring you into the
bond of the Covenant and I will Purge
out from among you the rebels and them
that transgress against me I will bring
them forth out of the country where they
sourn and they shall not enter into the
land of Israel and ye shall know that I
am the
Lord do not everybody every Israelite
every Hebrew Israelite is going through
the Wilderness just like it was when the
Lord brought us out of Egypt everyone is
going to the Wilderness but if you pay
but if you uh uh uh don't obey God you
would not come under under the bond of
the Covenant that's like get baptized in
Jesus name you'll never get out of it
just like your fathers you will be the
same read one more place Jude 5ifth
verse okay Jude five
says I will therefore put you in
remembrance though ye once knew this how
that the Lord having saved the people
out of the land of Egypt afterward
destroyed them that believe not
do not it's not so much as a matter of
getting in there the thing about it is
will you get out of
it
yep that's all I have to say all
right hope that shares some light as we
move on to our next question moving on
natley Charles says my mom is a devout
Catholic when she prays a blessing over
me she Anor my forehead and my hands
with oil by drawing a cross in the name
of the father Son and Holy Spirit I
heard that the cross on the forehead or
hand signify the mark of the beast is
this true should I let her anoint me or
should I refuse her
blessings all right good question there
brother Julius what you
say when you have sounds like you have
some uh you're at the age of reasoning I
would would not let her anoint me
anymore and you do your own
investigation on the origin of the cross
the cross is a Roman instrument of
capital punishment and torture I'm going
say it again the Tor the cross is a
Roman instrument of capital punishment
and torture that's what the Romans used
to punish people uh uh for going against
the empire and when you do the research
on the cross you will find out that this
is why they crucified true Christians
even Jesus himself was
crucified uh by way of the Cross So when
you say your mom is a devout Catholic
she is a devout Roman Catholic so she
has strong ties to her faith in that
right there so now you said that uh she
anointed your head by drawing a cross in
the name of the father son and Holy
Ghost and
and and that the cross on the forehead
and hand signify the mark it is a type
of image of the Beast of before the
image of the Beast comes I'm G show you
what I'm talking about but this is what
let's go to Mark the 8th chapter brother
James okay we got one more place after
this okay Mark 8 Mark 8 read verse
34 and when he had called the PE verse
34 yes and when he had called the people
unto him with his disciples also he said
unto them whosoever will come after me
let him deny himself and take up his
cross and follow me so he's telling you
you be ready to suffer and even die for
your faith for the gospel sake so this
is what the cross represents you know it
is it represents Roman capital
punishment and torture that is how the
Romans punish people and kill people by
way of crucifixion so Jesus didn't tell
you to wear a cross he said be ready to
suffer and even give your life for the
gospel's sake because the Romans was
ruling the world and that is the way
they punished and executed people let's
go to Revelation the 13th chapter
because this is where the Catholic
Church gets this from it's no accident
that they put it on your forehead and in
your right
hand Romans 13 my brother oh you said
was Romans or Revelation Revelation 13
I'm sorry Revelation
13 and when this man of sin come when
this religious head come look what he
gonna do verse 16 we gonna get right to
it okay it says and he causeth all both
small and great rich and poor free and
bond to receive a mark in their right
hand or in their foreheads and that's
exactly where your mother anoints you at
in the forehead and in the hand or the
right hand now but the time is going to
come and which you we waiting on this go
ahead at 17 and that no man might buy or
sell save he that had the Mark or the
name of the Beast or the number of his
name so
uh this is an economic embargo you can't
buy or sell unless you got this so
you're going to suffer you're going to
be if you don't have the the Mark or the
image you're going to suffer the number
you're going to suffer because it
represents capital punishment and
suffering so I would not let her anoint
me any anoint anymore uh anymore and
then you educate yourself and hopefully
show you a mom so
no no don't don't do it and do your own
research for and we got history books
that would tell you that there were the
Romans crucified 5002 Christians a day
and the book said that the crosses were
never bear so it is not an instrument of
God or Jesus Christ it is an instrument
of capital punishment and torture I hope
that
helped all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer that question
as we move on to our next one next one
sister Hur cat ask what age is
acceptable for children
fasting children fasting what age is
acceptable brother Dre what you
say well uh let's go to Isaiah the 28th
chapter this is an interesting verse
here because it tells
you let's let's read it Isaiah 28 verse
9 go ahead brother Whom Shall he teach
knowledge and Whom Shall he make to
understand Doctrine them that are wean
from the milk and drawn from the breast
now you got some children that will stay
on the breast until they six years old
you got to take them off of it you have
to wean them off of it but he asked the
question Whom Shall he teach knowledge
them that and make to understand
Doctrine them that are wean from the
milk and drawn from the breast so you
teach your children knowledge and you do
it when you weaning
them that's when knowledge is taught now
let's go to Proverbs the 26th chapter I
mean 22 Proverbs 22 and we going to read
verse six okay Proverbs and six train up
a child in the way he should go and when
he is old he will not depart from it
right and you start at the
beginning so I I hope that answers your
question in terms of fasting you train
them up in the way that they shall go
the only fast that is commanded is the
day of
atonement and it will not uh un alive
them for them to
fast but train them up in the way that
they shall
go those that are weaned from the breast
and drawn from the
milk I hope that
helps all right thank you for that
Brothers we move on to our next next one
Andre Jr asked in Leviticus 7: 37 and 38
are are these offerings the same that
was spoken of in Jeremiah 7 vers 21 and
22 all right brother Dre what you say
let's go read Jeremiah I mean Leviticus
7 37 and 38
may go ahead brother this is the law of
the burnt offering of the meat offering
and of the sin offering and of the
trespass offering and of the
consecrations and of the sacrifice of
the peace offerings which the Lord
commanded Moses in Mount Si in the day
that he commanded the children of Israel
to offer their oblations un the Lord in
the wilderness of Si now let's go to uh
Jeremiah 7 7 and before we read verse
21 to
23 Let's uh read Verse 18 Jeremiah 7
read Verse 18 and we G to skip okay the
children gather wood and the fathers
Kindle the fire and the women need their
dough to make cakes to the Queen of
Heaven and to pour out drink offerings
unto our gods and to other gods that may
Prov provoke me to anger so just by this
alone no this is not talking about the
same thing but verse 21 go ahead thus
sayeth the Lord of hosts the god of
Israel put your burnt offerings unto
your sacrifices and eat flesh for I
spake not unto your fathers nor
commanded them in the day that I brought
them out of the land of Egypt concerning
burnt offerings or sacrifices but this
thing commanded I them saying obey my
voice and I will be your God and ye
shall be my people and walk ye in all
the ways that I have commanded you that
in it may be well unto you and the very
next verse say but they hearken not
neither incline their ear so no this is
not to one God is commanding what they
should do here they didn't do it
that help yeah yes sir just obey his
voice Right Drake yes sir all right hope
that answers your question as we move on
moving on Fitness Guru asked in
Revelation 7 verse 9 does this number of
people in white robes include the people
from the Wilderness the Mars from the
Great Tribulation and the 144
th000 all right brother Jerome share
some light let's go read that verse um
Revelations 7 and9 I'm there go ahead
after this I beheld and low a great
multitude which no man could number of
all Nations and kindreds and people and
tongues stood Before the Throne and
before the lamb clothed with right robes
and and Palms in their hands
okay this this great multitude right
here I I want you to understand these
people weren't in the wilderness during
the time of the Great Tribulation which
is for three and a half years they not
in there they outside the Wilderness and
uh you also mentioned 144,000 which is
also in this same chapter they they
weren't uh in the wilderness either
during the time of the Great
Tribulation okay but everybody in this
chap
you know they they went through some of
the Great
Tribulation okay not all of it they
didn't go through all of it okay but
they went through some of it all right
but if they were in the wilderness they
wouldn't be going through no Great
Tribulation at all cuz they will be
protected there for the three and a half
years like like we read earlier today in
uh Revelations the 12th chapter the
woman that fled to the Wilderness and
she was nourished there for 3 and2 years
okay they not these people in this
chapter not a part of nobody that went
into their Wilderness during that time
okay uh but let's go to uh the second
verse read it to the four and we going
to skip okay and I saw another Angel
ascending from the East having the Seal
of the Living God and he cried with a
loud voice to the four angels to whom it
was given to hurt the earth and the Sea
saying hurt not the Earth neither the
sea nor the trees till we have sealed
the Servants of God in their foreheads
and I heard the number of them which
were sealed and they were
sealed 144,000 of all the tribes of the
children of Israel go
ahead of the tribe of Judah were sealed
12,000 of the tri four verse you read
you read the fourth verse already Yes
okay that that's good okay so they went
through some of the Great Tribulation
right but they didn't go through all of
it and the Lord sealed them so they they
weren't made martyrs so to speak they
weren't
killed
okay all right so skip down and read
verse n then we GNA go to verse 13 from
there okay verse 9 says after this I
beheld in low a great multitude which no
man could number of all Nations and
kindred and people and tongues stood
Before the Throne and before the lamb
clothed with white robes and Palms in
their heads so they were sealed too but
they did go through some of that great
Great Tribulation but they weren't
killed or martyred okay read skip down
to verse 13 read to the 14 and one of
the elders answered saying unto me what
are these which are arrayed in white
robes and whence came they and I said
unto to him sir thou knowest and he said
to me these are they which came out of
the Great Tribulation and have washed
their robes and made them white in the
blood of the Lamb yeah and and if you
read the rest of that chapter the Lord
going to feed them with that word cuz
they ain't in the first resurrection
either so they going to still have to be
feed the word of God okay that's all I
got
on all right thank you for that as we we
move on to our next question next
question Malik Shakur asked in Matthew
24 verse 20 why should we pray that our
flight is not on the Sabbath I think I
understand the winter but why not on the
Sabbath let's go there and read that
because certain parts of the
area that some people will be going
through they honor the Sabbath so stuff
be shut down and getting tight but God
will still make a way but read that
verse
20 but pray that your flight be not in
the winter neither on the Sabbath day
because you say you understand the
winter yeah it's a little tougher to
travel then during the winter you know
cancel flights all kind of stuff but on
the Sabbath day you be part of the area
over there celebrate the Sabbath so they
shut down and try and honor the Sabbath
and things will be tight so hey if you
can avoid that that winter time you know
when the weather can be bad and you can
avoid um you know neither on the Sabbath
day when they shutting down and things
will be moving a lot
quicker and that's all I
get all right we hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
next one MJ hello asks how do you how do
you know when you have received the gift
of the Holy Ghost after baptism brother
Julius how do you
know when you come out when you don't do
the things that you used to do before
you went into the
water you be you come out of that water
a new creation as the brother said
earlier you're not the same person
everybody wants to jump and get the Holy
Ghost nobody wants to repent and
acknowledge their transgression so you
get you have understanding of what the
let's look at what the book say let's go
to St John the 14th
chapter and this is how you really know
St John the 14th chapter and that's I
want verse 15 I want verse 15 I want to
emphasize verse 15 St John 14 James and
read 15 if ye love me keep my
Commandments if you love me keep my
Commandments skip all the way down
that's to verse 21 and go ahead he that
hath my command ments and keepeth them
he it is that loveth me and he that
loveth me shall be loved of my father
and I will love him and will manifest
myself to him skip down to verse 26 go
ahead and read it but the comforter
which is the Holy Ghost whom the father
will send in my name he shall teach you
all things and bring all thing you going
you going to have understanding of the
laws statutes and Commandments of God go
ahead and bring all things to your
remembrance whatsoever I have said unto
you so when you got that Holy Ghost you
going to walk in the law commandment you
not I don't steal no more I don't I
don't want to do no harm to my neighbor
I want to remember the Sabbath day and
keep it holy let's go to 1st Samuel the
10th
chapter you become a whole another
person 1st Samuel 10
and pick it up at verse one real quick
go ahead James then Samuel took a vile
of oil and ported upon his head and
kissed him and said is it not because
the Lord ha anointed thee to be Captain
over his inheritance this is talk about
with Saul when the Lord chose Saul verse
six go
ahead and the spirit of the Lord will
come upon thee and thou shalt prophesy
with them and shalt be turned into
another man man and you GNA become
another person skip down to verse nine
and go ahead and it was so that when he
had turned his back to go from Samuel
God gave him another heart and all those
signs came to pass that day in other
words another heart is another way of
thinking you walk into the law statutes
and Commandments of God you don't want
to sin against your neighbor you going
to love your wife you're going to love
your husband so that's the best I can do
with that when you get when the when the
Holy Spirit really comes upon you you
become a new person you you're not the
old person that you used to be all you
think about is doing your best to keep
God's laws statutes and Commandments I
hope that
helped yes sir keep them laws How Sweet
It
Is all right I hope that ansed your
question as we move on to our next next
one Jennifer Love says I know that the
Bible states to honor thy mother and it
doesn't specify
conditions what do you do when your
parents don't want to talk to you to
resolve past issues regardless of how
often you
try what do you do guest
caller if it's not if it's not a matter
of life and death leave it
alone good
all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next next
one Epatha says please explain Daniel 4
verse
13 a watcher I know Hebrews 2 vers 13
and 14 States the angels are ministering
Spirits why is the term Watchers used
here why is the term Watchers used
brother
Jerome let's go read those verses that
you gave Daniels 4 and 13 and then
Hebrews actually you got Hebrews 2 in
your question but you probably referring
to Hebrews 1 but let's go read that
Daniels first okay Daniel 4 and3 said I
saw in the visions of my head upon my
bed and behold a watcher and un Holy One
came down from
heaven okay now let's go to the
Hebrews okay and I'm there um Hebrews
Hebrews two read the two first because
that's how they got it in the question 2
14 uh Hebrews 2 verse 13- 14 says and
again I will put my trust in him and
again behold I and the children which
God ha given me for as much as the
children are partakers of Flesh and
Blood he also himself likewise took part
of the same that through death he might
destroy him that had the power of death
that is the devil yeah so those verses
really don't have anything to do with
your question so let's try that chapter
one and read verse 13- 14 that's more
connected to your
question chapter one yeah 13 and 14
but to which of the Angels said he at
any time sit on my right hand until I
make thine enemies thy foot stol are
they not all ministering Spirits sent
forth to minister for them who shall be
HS of
Salvation okay now in that D when it
mentioned Watchers it said Watchers that
came down from heaven and those are
those are angels okay
and I want to read a verse in
Revelations that's similar to this title
Watcher that's given to an angel I'm
going to show you a similar title um
that's kind of meaning the same thing
okay so let's go to the revelations
5 okay and we're going to read verse six
okay Revelation 5 and verse 6 says and I
beheld and lo in the midst of the throne
and of the four beasts and in the midst
of the Elders stood a lamb as it had
been slain having seven horns and seven
eyes which are the seven spirits of God
sent forth into all the Earth it's that
bottom part of that verse I want you to
focus on it where it talk about the
seven eyes the seven Eyes Of God that he
sent forth to and they they got them
seven them seven they watching okay okay
and um we would uh you you got the these
cherubim angels and they got eyes all
over the place all on their wings and
stuff and them eyes ain't there for
nothing they watching okay but that's
all I got if anybody want to add
something all right I think they hit it
hit it on the head I think
Zechariah talks about it I think
Zechariah fourth chapter tell with the
seven eyes oh of God yeah four
talk about the same on seven lamps
talking about seven angels and and uh uh
and these eyes let me see what's it
four Zar 4 um yeah it up at that verse
10 that's yeah so Zechariah 4 Zechariah
4 and verse
well just start at the
top okay Zechariah 4 And1 says and the
angel that talked with me came again and
waked me as a man that is waken out of
his
sleep go and said unto me what seeth
thou and I said I have looked and behold
a Candlestick all of gold with a bowl
upon the top of it and a seven lamps
there on and and seven pipes to the
seven lamps which are upon the top
thereof and these seven lamps in
Revelation fourth chapter will tell you
that they are the spirits of God but
still skip down to verse 10 and and read
it for who hath despised the day of
small things for they shall rejoice and
shall see the plumet in the hand of
zerubabel with those seven they are the
eyes of the Lord which run to and fro
through the whole
earth those that are Watchers them seven
angels they looking everywhere all over
the earth watching
everything so the brother was right I
just wanted to put that in
it all right hope that ansers your
question there sister Deborah I believe
we going into new territory with a Time
Check Yes the time is
8:20 we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday February 26
2025 Randy Sims asked in Second Kings 24
verse4 and 2 Kings 251 and 12 the king
of Babylon took all Jerusalem who was
these people that was in the land that
became Vine dressers and husand Men all
right brother Julius who was these
people let's go let's go to the
scripture then read it I'm there read
verse Second Kings 24 and4 go ahead
brother and he carried away all
Jerusalem and all the princes and all
the Mighty Men of Valor even 10,000
captives and all the Craftsmen and
Smiths none remained save the poorest
sort of the people of the land now let's
go to the 25th
chapter 25th chapter and read verse 11
and
12 now the rest of the people that were
left in the city and the fugitives that
fell away to the king of Babylon with
the remnant of the multitude did never
nebar Adan the captain of the Guard
carry away but the captain of the Guard
left of the poor of the land to be Vine
dressers and husband
men so Vine dressers are people that
prun
and take care of the Great Vines because
the king is Israel is still in captivity
so they're the poor of the land but they
were left to dress the uh the prune and
to keep The
Vineyards okay to keep the grapes so
they can grow the grapes and the husband
men that's a ancient name or old name
for our modern day Farmers so the
husband men took care of the crops they
grow the crops crops and the raw
materials that came from the crops so
when Nebuchadnezzar wanted wine he said
hey bring me some wine from Jerusalem
when he want to building materials and
food and stuff go because they were left
in the land to take care of the land for
wine dressers and for a farmers that's
what the answer to that is and when you
are poor you are in no Authority and
have no power so he used those people to
to uh farm the land and
to uh make the wine that's the best we
could do with
that all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next one
next one Epatha as in Luke
24 verse
39 Jesus said a spirit have not Flesh
and Bones as he had reading Four Winds
of Heaven page
76 third paragraph States new body will
be made from old he was flesh and
spirit all right I'm go to Luke 24 and
39 and then the guess caller take it
from there
okay I'm there Luke 24 and
39 says behold my hands and my feet that
it is I myself handle me and see for a
spirit ha not Flesh and Bones as ye see
me
have okay that that that's nothing new
uh before Jesus came in in uh Came In
the Flesh he did that with Abraham all
he did was M maintain a human form uh uh
uh he was spirit being now just took on
a human form just his Apostles so they
would know that that is him there ain't
no such thing as SP spirit and SP uh uh
flesh let me go see let's go into uh uh
let's go into uh uh
Genesis Genesis the uh uh uh 18th
chapter read 1 through five and then
skip down and read eight okay Genesis 18
1-5 and then verse 8 says and the Lord
appeared unto him in the plains of
mammory and he sat in the tent Door In
the Heat of the day and he lift his eye
he lift up his eyes and looked and loow
three men stood by him and when he saw
them he ran to meet them from the tent
door and bowed himself toward the ground
and said my Lord if now I have found
favor in thy sight pass not away I pray
thee from thy servant let a little water
I pray you be fetched and wash your feet
and rest yourselves under the tree and I
will fetch a
Mor now these guys what what what
Abraham saw was God and two angels what
he said they three men they look just
like men just like Jesus Took on the
form after it had come out the grave but
finish that and I will fetch a morsel of
bread and comfort ye your hearts after
that ye shall pass on for there for are
ye come to your servant and they said so
do as thou has
said in verse verse eight says and he
took butter and milk and the calf which
he had dressed and set it before them
and he stood by them under the tree and
they did
eat so the whole thing is they look like
men and they ate like men but they were
Spirit beings all spirit being you can't
uh uh you can't uh uh uh uh uh be in
between let's look at something here
let's go into uh uh
uh 1 Corinthians the 15th chapter read
verse 35 and Skip down and read verse 40
and
44 okay that was 1 Corinthians
15 verse was that what was the first
verse again
sir verse uh 35 okay verse 35 says so 1
Corinthians 15:35 says but some men will
say how are the dead raised up and with
what body do they
come go ahead get down to
40 verse 40 says there are also
celestrial bodies and bodies terrestrial
but the glory of the celestial is one
and the glory of the terrestrial is
another go ah there is one glory of the
Sun and another glory of the Moon and
another glory of the stars for one star
differeth from another star in
glory so all is the resurrection also is
the resurrection of the dead it is sown
in corruption it is raised in corruption
it is sown in dishonor it is raised in
glory it is sown in weakness it is
raised in power it is sown a natural
body it is raised a spiritual body there
is a natural body and there is a
spiritual
body and that's what we have he was
flesh and blood and he showed up and he
let them and and and uh and and showed
the Apostle himself as he was when he
walked about him when he walked around
with him but he was a spirit body he
said flesh and Bone but then can they
inherit
this kingdom of
God let's have a look and see get down
to
49 and read the 51 okay verse 49 says
and as we have borne the image of the
earthy we shall also bear the image of
the Heavenly now this I say Brethren
that flesh and blood cannot inherit the
kingdom of God neither doeth corruption
inherit
incorruption behold I show you a mystery
we shall not all asleep but we shall all
be
changed now this the whole thing is
flesh and blood cannot inherit the the
kingdom of God you have to be changed
and all of Jesus was changed and what I
stated and uh uh uh uh and what we read
earlier it said everybody have to be
changed otherwise you can't get in the
kingdom of God so you can't be has
spirit and has flesh you have to be all
Spirit All
Flesh what said about the first man Adam
he was made a living Soul right second
man Adam was made a quicker in spirit so
now Jesus just showed up in his flesh
form for his Apostles sake just like he
showed up in his flesh form for
Abraham's
sake that's all I have to say all right
I hope that answers your question as we
move on to our next one next one she
also asked for
explanation uh in Galatians 3 verse
23 explain before Faith came we were
under law I partially understand but
need more
precepts right so brother Dre help her
to understand more let's let's go to
that Galatians 3 and see what it's
talking about so you
read read verse 23 and we gonna bag up a
little bit go ahead brother but before
Faith came we were kept under the law
shut up unto the faith which should
afterwards be revealed
which should afterwards be revealed now
this faith is in Christ but bag up and
read verse
16 now to Abraham and his seed were the
promises made he saith not into to seeds
as of many but as of one and to thy seed
which is Christ and that promise is that
in Abraham's seed shall all nations of
of the earth be blessed read verse 19 go
ahead brother wherefore then serveth the
law it was added because of
transgressions till the seed should come
to whom the pro the uh promise was made
and it was ordained by angels in the
hand of a mediator so he says wherefore
then serveth the law it was added
because a law was broken because of
transgressions till the seed should come
to whom the promise was made that seed
is
Christ now the promise was in that seed
shall all nations of the earth be
blessed and that law that was added
because of
transgression was the sacrificial law
read verse 23
again but before Faith came we were kept
under the law shut up unto to the faith
which should afterwards be revealed go
ahead brother wherefore the law was our
school Master to bring us unto Christ
that we might be justified by
faith that's right read the next verse
but after that faith has come we are no
longer under a school master that school
the sacrificial law that pointed to
Christ go go ahead read the next
verse for ye are all the children of God
by faith in Christ Jesus uhhuh for as
many of you as have been baptized into
Christ have put on Christ that's right
there go that baptism again buried with
him in baptism raised to walk in the
newness of light but that law that is
talking about in Galatians is the
sacrificial law that was added because
of sin until the seed should come who
was the ultimate sacrifice and you can
read about more about that in Hebrews
the 10th
chapter so I hope that
helps all right thank you for that
brother as we move on to our next
question moving on Glenn Sirius ask can
I be circumcise and baptize if I'm
unclean uh not sure
exactly what you may mean by that
question but these are two different
things taking place here now you can get
circumcised sure and you have to do that
before you can be baptized and when you
talking about uncleanness yeah there's
certain uncleanness that can take place
and you can still be circumcised but
then once you start to heal and once you
have healed now and you still desire to
be baptized and you can be baptized but
there's still certain things that you
have to do so that you don't make
yourself unclean so that you can partake
in the baptism so you don't want to
touch your dead body you don't want to
have any open cuts and sores that's not
healing you don't want to have any any
earns you know in your home so these are
two different things that's taking place
you have to be circumcised first and
then you have to be baptized and you
have to follow everything that pertains
to keeping you clean for the baptism
women can be on a monthly and other
things like that and that's all I got
anybody
else all right we gonna leave it right
there and we're gonna move on to our
next question next question ran 64 asks
when the Bible talks about Thrones for
judging people will these Thrones only
be used in the second Resurrection or
other periods of time during the one th
year reign all right tell us a little
more about these Thrones brother
Jerome yeah um those sitting on those
Thrones you talking about which is I
believe Revelations the 20th chapter
verse uh
four yeah those Thrones they gonna be
used in uh during the uh as you called
it the second
Resurrection after the second
Resurrection going to be the white
throne judge me they going to be used
there obviously but the same on sitting
on those Thrones they going to be
judging various things going on during
the thousand year reign of Christ too
you know so let's go to uh First
Corinthians chapter
6 and read verse 1 and two and then we
going to go to Revelations the second
chapter after
that brother J yeah First
Corinthians chapter 6 verse 1 and two go
ahead it says dare any of you having a
matter against another go to go to law
before the unjust and not before the
Saints do ye not know that the Saints
shall judge the world and if the world
shall be judged by you are ye unworthy
to judge the smallest
matters yeah so yeah the saints that
come up in their first resurrection they
going to be sitting on thron and they
going to be judging through Millennium
and I think it said uh the Lord told the
12 apostles he said you should be
judging the the uh 12 tribes of Israel
that's going to be going on during
during the um thousand year reign of
Christ you know and then he got those
that He said those that are overcome he
said since you were Faithful over a few
things I'm going to make you ruler over
many things and and he told him he said
I'm going to give you 10 cities I'm
going to give you 20 you know cities to
judge over okay so uh one more place
let's go to Revelations 2 verse 20 huh
yeah Revelations 2 verse 26 through
27 okay that'll be it and he that
overcometh and keepeth my works until
the end to him will I give power over
the Nations and he shall rule the with a
rod of iron as the vessels of a Potter
shall they be broken to Shivers even as
I received of my father yeah that's all
I got
on all right yes sir everybody on this
panel is shooting for that first
resurrection all right moving on to our
next question moving on genius Beauties
asked Are there women prophetes today
there women prophetes today brother
Julius uh not according to the Bible not
in the way that God Called It the Bible
is complete it is written and it is
complete so let's go to job the 32nd
chapter because everybody wants to jump
up and have titles I'm a prophet Prophet
so say prophetes such and such let's
look at what the Bible said about these
titles
James uh read job 32 verse 21 21 and 22
go ahead my brother let me not I pray
you accept any man's person neither let
me give flattering titles unto man be
careful be careful about trying to
obtain a title verse 22 go ahead for I
know not to give flattering titles in so
doing my maker would soon take me away
now let's go to Matthew the 24th
chapter if you desire to be a prophet or
a
prophetess you can't be one cuz the book
told you the prophet from Moses to
John the Bible is
complete Matthew 24 my brother read four
and five go ahead and read it and Jesus
answered and said unto them take heed
that no man deceive you for many shall
come in my name saying I am Christ and
shall deceive many and shall deceive
many and and when and what does that
when you deceive many coming in name of
Jesus what do you become verse
11 and many false prophets shall rise
and shall deceive many so you got a
whole lot of false prophets around here
and false prophetesses why because they
are Antichrist the Bible is written it
is complete so therefore you can become
a false prophet or a prophetess so now
what do we do here at the Israel of God
the best that we do is prophesy that
means to speak that which is already
written because we do not have the
latitude to add or take away from
anything so we speak that which is
written that don't make us
prophets we just Serv as of
God that's all I got and on your own you
can read Revelation um you can read
Revelation where
Jezebel called herself a prophetes but
she was not working for
God that's all I
got all right thank you for that hope
that answer that question next one
sister with the time Check Yes next one
8:40 is the time Epatha says in 1 Peter
3: 19 and 20 he preached Spirit he
preached Spirits in prison which were
dis dis obedient in Noah's days uh
explain I need
Clarity all right Clarity is on the way
let's go to that first Peter 3 brother
James read that 19 and 20 and then the
guest caller will bring some clarity
from there okay 1 Peter 3:19 says by
which also he went and preached unto the
spirits in prison which sometime were
disobedient when Once the longsuffering
of God waiting in the day in the days of
Noah while the ark was are preparing
were in few that is eight Souls were
saved and we need we need to start that
just a little higher okay when he said
he was put
the Death In the Flesh back up a little
bit and get it from the
top okay
um you want me go to 16 start back at
17 oh go to 16 what 16 say 16 says
having a good conscience that whereas
they speak evil of you as of evildoers
they may be ashamed that falsely accused
your good conversation in
Christ that's first Peter 3:19 and 20
you read oh I'm sorry 1 Peter 19 3 and9
says but which also he went and preached
unto the spirits in
prison and verse 18 says for Christ also
hath once suffered for sins the just for
the you gota so you have to you just
can't start and make statement you have
to see what came into that so now Christ
once suffer for sin go ahead and read
the just for the unjust that he might
bring us to God God being put to death
in the flesh but quickened by the
spirit now put to death that mean he
died as a f Flesh and Blood being and
then he made he was made alive as a
spirit
being
now you can read the rest and we'll deal
with it okay verse 19 says by which also
he went and preached unto the spirits in
prison which sometime were disobedient
when Once the longsuffering of God
waited in the days of Noah while the ark
was a preparing were in few that is
eight Souls were saved by
water okay so now all this saying is
that Jesus died in the flesh and he Rose
when he rose he was quick and a Made
Alive in the spirit in other words when
he rose he was a spirit being and he was
in that same form
when he went back and preach when he uh
preached rather to the spirits in Noah's
day so that give you a time so these
Disobedience disobedient Spirits was in
the days of Noah so Jesus and and and
and uh uh the Lord had him in prison we
sure how but Jesus had to preach to him
apparently they got uh uh uh they got
the uh uh out of hand I want you to read
1 Corinthians 15
and read verse 42 to 47 let's look at
something here okay verse F I'm sorry 1
Corinthians 15 ver
46 42- 47 42- 47 says so also is the
resurrection of the dead it is sown in
corruption it is raised in
incorruption it is sown in dishonor it
is raised in glory it is sown in weak
it is raised in power it is swn a
natural body it is raised a spiritual
body there is a natural body and there
is a spiritual body and so it is and so
it is written the first man Adam was
made a living Soul the last Adam was
made a quickening spirit how be it that
was not first which is spiritual but
that which is natural and after that
which is spiritual the first man is of
the earth earthy the second man is of
the Lord From
Heaven so when Jesus died and rose from
the dead he was a Living spirit a spirit
being just like he was in the days of
Noah let's show you and then he was God
again read verse 4 and uh uh go to John
4 and 24 and show you what God is St
John 424
John John uh 4: 24 says God is a spirit
and they that worship Him must worship
Him in spirit and in truth so Jesus was
God so then if Jesus went back to being
God he was a spirit again so now in the
days of
Noah when he was a spirit being he
preached to the uh uh uh Spirits in
prison to make sure that there was Jesus
back there read St John 5 and
37 John 5 and verse 37 says and the
father himself which has sent me have
borne witness of me ye have neither
heard his voice at any time nor seen his
shape and no and that covers any time
covers all time so it let you know that
the god in the days of Noah was Jesus
and he was and being God he was a spirit
like he is now now let's show you
something here we want to
know who are these Spirits in prison go
to Second
Peter read verse 2 and
4 I mean to Second Peter chapter 2 and
verse4 okay second Peter chapter 2 and
verse4 says for if God spared not the
angels that sin but cast them down to
Hell and delivered them into chains of
Darkness to be reserved unto
judgment and they're
still in prison under chains of Darkness
they can't stop jump up in front of you
or shoot appear in front of you and so
they got unruly in the days of Noah
these are angels he talking about but to
make sure that you know what these
angels are go to Hebrews the first
chapter read verse 7 and Skip down to
verse 14 and read it
okay
Hebrews one you said Hebrews 1 correct
sir ver chapter verse 7 and verse 14
okay Hebrews 1 and7 says and the and of
the angels He saith who maketh his
angels spirits and his ministers a flame
of
fire and then verse 14 says are they not
all ministering Spirits sent forth to
minister for them who shall be HS of
Salvation so the spirit that he preached
to was the angel that was disobedient in
the days of Noah while Noah Was
preparing the AR all this saying here in
the uh uh in First Peter the 3 chapter
that Jesus was put to death death as a
flesh and blood
being but he rose rose being made alive
as a spirit
being the same type being the having the
same type body that he had in the days
of Noah when he had to preach to them
angels that was disobedient in Noah's
time but a lot of people saying when
Jesus died he went in the grave and
preached to the that's talk about when
he speak uh uh preached to the dead
people in the grave first thing is dead
people in the grave are not Spirit they
were s their
souls so all they're saying is that
Jesus once he rose from the dead he was
a spirit being again and that's and
that's the same and and that's what he
was when he preached to them disobedient
angels in the days of Noah while David
Noah Was preparing the AR that's all I
have to say all right hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
question as time is a ticket yes next
question co cool blue says does God tell
in the Bible what we should not drink to
get
drunk all right brother Dre what you say
what we should not drink what we should
not drink to get
drunk let's go to Proverbs 20 and we
just gonna read verse one there go ahead
brother okay Proverbs 20 and one says
wine is a mocker strong drink is Raging
and whosoever is deceived thereby is not
wise so you can be deceived by it and it
is not wise to be deceived by excessive
drinking let's go to Proverbs 23 read
verse 29 and 30 and we G to skip and
read one more verse there okay Proverbs
23 and 29 and 30 says who hath woe who
hath sorrow who hath contentions who ha
Bab
who have wounds without cause who have
redness of eyes they that tar long at
the wine that they go to seek mixed wine
they that t long at the wine and they
that go to seek mixed wine verse 35 go
ahead they have stricken me shalt thou
say and I was not sick they have beaten
me and I felt it not when shall I awake
I will seek it yet again that's that's a
problem but let's go to Ephesians 5 and
we going to read Verse 18 and that'll be
it go ahead brother when you get it okay
Ephesians
5 and what was the verse again 18
Ephesians 5 and8 says and be not drunk
with wine wherein it where in is excess
but be filled with the spirit so it
ain't nothing wrong with drinking WI
wine but it says don't be drunk with
wine wearing is excess but be filled
with the
spirit I hope that
helped Another Place Another Place that
said that don't try to get master here
over strong drin is right if you going
to try to master it that mean you it's
going to master you cuz you're going to
drink too
much
all all right
gonna be out there driving drunk
breaking the law of the
land all right let's move on to our next
one they also
ask or they also say my job has made it
mandatory that we work Saturday and I
can't get Saturdays off what do I do
quit no you should be in job search
right now if you're looking to get the
Sabbath off in job search and when you
find you a job that allows for you to
have the Sabbath off then hey then you
can tell that other job give them your
week's notice or two weeks notice rather
and then you move on to your job that
allow for you to have the Sabbath offer
but hey pray that the Lord help to make
the change for you that's all I
got as we move on to our next question
moving on I chug Wu Arman asks are there
any biblical or scriptural significance
for people to be
buried in their homelands countes states
or cities where they were
born right being buried where you was
born brother Julius what you
say only if it's delegated by God such
as Abraham he was called out of his
country and to the land of Canaan and
Abraham Isaac and Jacob all them died in
the land of Canaan which is modern day
Israel Jesus but no really no real
significance I'm G show you what the
book says St John 5 James James St John
5 and verse
24 St John 5 and 24 says uhhuh verily
verily I say unto you he that heareth my
word and believeth on him that sent me
have everlasting life and shall not come
into condemnation but has passed from
Death unto life keep going verily verily
I say unto you the hour is coming and
now coming go ahead and now is when the
dead shall hear the voice of the Son of
God and they that hear shall live it
says the dead don't it let's go to
Revelation the 20th
chapter pray that you be in the first
resurrection I don't care where I'm
buried at I am in a in a country of my
captivity if I pass away here and I'm
right the Lord GNA wake me
up it's how you living in what you know
not so much as the location Revelation
20 my brother okay and pick it up at
verse
um uh let's see read verse
six okay blessed and holy is he that
hath part in the first resurrection what
we shooting for that's what we all
should be shooting for that first
resurrection go ahead on such the second
death have no power but they shall be
Priests of God and of Christ and shall
reign with him a thousand years now
after a thousand years let's go to verse
11 and go
ahead and I saw a great white throne and
him that sat on it from whose face the
earth and the heaven fled away and there
was found no place for them go ahead
and I saw the dead small and great stand
before God and the books were open and
another book was open which is The Book
of Life and the dead were judged out of
those things which were written in the
books according to their Works they was
resurrected give me verse
13 and the Sea gave up the dead which
were in
it all the people that died and was that
and their bodies died in the sea where
however they died in the sea not no land
not not no location wherever they died
at the book said the sea gave it the
dead which were what were in it uhhuh
and death and Hell delivered up the dead
which were in them and they were and
they were judged every man according to
their works so sisters and brothers it's
not the location it is the mindset how
you liveing and what you know when you
die that's why you got to keep your
garments always white and Jesus said if
you love me keep my Commandments and in
keeping of the command is a great reward
what eternal life that's the best I can
do with
that all right we're going to move on to
our next question next question
commissioner Paula a safer asks are
there any iog Productions that explain
the way of Salvation that I can email to
family and others as a
Evangelistic tool
all right I'm not getting that
Evangelistic tool P we'll open that up
to the panel but um yeah there's a lot
of lessons that you can um email to
somebody if you trying to bring them
into the truth but they also have to
have something as well let's go to
Matthew 11 read one verse let's go to
Matthew
11 and let's read that verse
15 okay Matthew 11 and 15 say says he
that hath ears to hear Let Him hear that
is key when you trying to share a word
with somebody they got to have ears to
hear because if they don't want to hear
nothing you got to say then it ain't
gonna make no difference turn over to
Revelation three Revelation
three and let's pick it up at that verse
20 Revelation 3 and 20 go ahead behold I
stand at the door and knock If any man
hear my voice and open the door I will
come in to him and will sub with him and
he with
me to him that overcometh will I grant
to sit with me in my throne even as I
also overcame and have sat down with my
father in his throne yeah go ahead he
that hath an ear let him hear what the
spirit saith unto the churches so yes
there's a lot of things that you can um
email them when it comes to Salvation
you can even we have a lesson called
salvation what would you trade for it
that is also a good one so they have to
want to hear it and have to want to
receive it and now it's open to the
panel on this Evangelistic tool so uh
brother Corel the way I do it I turn
people on I tell them to get the iog app
or either go to your YouTube and pick
you a lesson go to and pick you a
lessons scroll down and find you a
lesson all of it pertains to
Salvation that's correct and yeah like
you say so many angles we can take hey
we are having our black history series
lesson and that is a five-part series
which will'll explain the last one at
the end of the show but uh sister deil
let's move on to our next oh what time
is it um it's nine but this one you can
answer very quick Qui they want to know
is it a sin to smoke while reading or
studying the
Bible so brother Jerome can you smoke
that toy while you are reading the
Bible let's go to First John the thir
chapter verse four I'm
there go ahead and read it whosoever
committeth sin
transgresses also the law for sin is the
transgression of the law
that's all I got on
that all
right go ahead yeah this other one here
about the Sabbath day when it
starts uh the panel can yeah can answer
this uh Zion says if a day starts at
evening and the Sabbath Stars Friday
evening wouldn't we be sleeping most of
the Sabbath
all right so open to the panel because
we know that the day does start at the
evening open to the panel listen some
people work at night yep back you
sleeping some people work all night and
they don't sleep it all depends on the
time of the year in the
person that's all need to be said about
that and we got this uh final question
here gas colge you want to address that
one why not
all right sister go ahead all right ANC
says from a previous Q&A the guest
caller had made a distinction between
comforter and Holy Ghost saying
comforter refer to angels in John 14
verse 26 it says the comforter is the
Holy Ghost can you clarify this also in
Luke 1 verse 34 and
35 would Gabriel be considered a
comforter since he's an angel then
shouldn't Gabriel himself be the Holy
Ghost why does he say the Holy Ghost
will come upon Mary this is
confusing yes go which thing is you keep
using uh comfor in Holy Ghost let's do
something here first of all let's see uh
uh let's let's uh uh uh uh you know like
look go to Hebrews the first
chapter okay and we going to find out
what a spirit is because they keep you
that word holy ghost ghost is slang for
Spirit okay through all places you see
Holy Ghost it should be saying holy
spirit so Hebrews 1 read 7 and
14 okay Hebrews 1:7 says and of the
angels He saith who maketh his angels
spirits and his ministers a flame of
fire verse 14 says are they not all
ministering Spirits sent forth to
minister for them who shall be hes of
Salvation okay so we Angel the spirit
that tell us that does it now just go to
Matthew's 25th chapter and read verse 31
okay that was Matthew 24 and verse
right it says and he shall send his
angels with a great sound of a trumpet
and they shall gather together his elect
from the Four Winds from one end of
Heaven to the other wait a I'm
sorry you you reading verse 31 25 and 31
oh I'm sorry that was 24 and 3 1 verse
25 and 31 says when the son of man shall
come in his glory and all the angels
with him then shall he sit upon the
throne of his
glory read that again when the son of
man shall come in his glory and all the
Holy Angels with him then shall he
sit that's the word there cometh his
glory and all the Holy Angels with them
so if they're holy and they're Spirit
what does that make them Holy Spirit
Holy Angels Holy Spirit every one of our
holy spirit all of the Angels now let's
show you here let's go into Exodus the
28th chapter read verses 20 and
21 Exodus
28 no Exodus 23 oh
23 Exodus 23 and what was
the
20 21 20 21 it says behold I sent an
angel before thee to keep thee in the
way and to bring thee into the place
which I have prepared beware of him and
obey his voice provoke him not for he
will not pardon your transgressions for
my name is in
him okay let's let's follow and see if
it see if uh uh it Israel obeyed the
Lord go to Isaiah the 633rd chapter
Isaiah
chapter chapter 63 and read from 8 to
10 Isaiah
63 and vers
8-10 says for he said surely they are my
people children that will not lie so he
was their Savior and all their
Affliction he was afflicted and the
angel of his presence saved them in his
love and and in his pity he redeemed
them and he bare them and carried them
all the days of old but they rebelled
rebelled and vexed his holy spirit
therefore he was turned to be their
enemy and he fought against them so this
angel that he sent before him to lead
him in the way he is the holy spirit
ain't that's what the book say yes
sir oh so the comforter the Lord say he
would comfort you how cuzz he going to
send you a comforter who in that
comforter an angel Holy Angel if it's
gab also he is an angel and he is a Holy
Angel so all can look and and so that's
how the Lord comfort
you through his holy spirit with your
Holy Angels now the other part of this
was uh about uh uh what was the last
part about
uh um the yes uh she's uh they stay why
does he say the Holy Ghost will come
upon
Mary okay because
uh he delivered a package and let's see
what that package
is let's go into uh
uh Hebrews the 10th chapter we're going
to read verse one then we going to skip
down and read verse four and 5 okay
Hebrews 10 verse1 verse says for the law
having a shadow of good things to come
and not the very image of the things can
never with those sacrifices which they
offered year by year continually make
the comers there unto perfect verse
four couldn't make it perfect you
couldn't become God by killing animals
so he needed so skip down to verse four
and tell you why verse four says for it
is not possible that the blood of bulls
and of goats should take away
sins verse five says wherefore when he
cometh into the world he saith sacrifice
and offering thou wouldest not but a
body has has thou prepared
me now Jesus Is God spirit being
couldn't
die man needed some God needed the
father needed somebody to sacrifice for
sin so he needed a body so the father
prepared him a
body and what happened he gave it to an
angel let's go in 139th chapter of Psalm
in verse 13 this is the last
place okay Psalms
139 and thir 13 says for thou H has
possessed my Reigns thou has covered me
in my mother's
womb now this R this this is his body so
that body that was P that uh uh uh that
the father made for him that angel which
is the Holy
Spirit come upon Mary and planted that
baby what did it what did he say covered
me and my mother's what covered me and
my mother's womb he took that body and
he put that body in Mary's womb and he
went to n B and he was born so that Holy
Ghost which is the holy SP spirit that
come upon Mary was an angel and what was
he doing he was delivering that body
that the father had made for Jesus
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answers your question our final
question of the evening and we'd like to
thank everybody from all around the
world who tuned in with us we enjoyed
being with you but if you submitted a
question and we didn't have an
opportunity to get to it please don't
resubmit it sister de will take it put
it in rotation and we will address your
question next week and we also like to
remind you that this is our final leg of
black history our final series titled
the adoption please join us at 520 West
138th Street in Riverdale
60827 so you can see further Insight on
black history and I final lay the
adoption so until we all come together
again be safe out there be blessed stay
prayed up and may the Lord have mercy on
us all as brother James closes us out
Our Father which art in heaven Hallowed
be thy name thy kingdom come thy will be
done in earth as it is in heaven give us
this day our daily bread and forgive us
our debts as we forgive our debors and
lead us not into temptation but Deliver
Us from Evil for thine is the kingdom
and the power and the glory forever in